Alexandra Campbell - AKA Ali. Designer gone full stack web developer.

Dedicated programmer coming from a background in industrial design and graphics. I

love scripting digital experiences for people and can offer a range of both creative and technical skills. Always ready to work with any new tools for the job.

### CONTACT

Ali Campbell 1+ (602) 625-2503 AlexandraBrinnCampbell@gmail.com







## DEV

JavaScript • React • Enzyme • ¡Query • HTML5 • CSS/Sass • Bootstrap • Node.is Ruby on Rails
SQL
PostgreSQL MVC architecture • OOP • git • GitHub • Heroku

## UX & UI

Webflow • Invision • Adobe Creative Suite Sketch • Figma • Whimsical • Mindnode AutoCad • user interviews & testing • branding & creative content

#### **EDUCATION**

MAY 2019 - CURR

Thinkful. JavaScript, Node Fullstack **Engineering Program** 

JAN - MAR 2019

Le Wagon, London. Ruby on Rails Coding Bootcamp

FEB - MAR 2018

General Assembly 8 week course in UX design

BDES INDUSTRIAL DESIGN, 2007

**Emily Carr University, Vancouver BC** 

## **PROJECTS**

## Doctors Near Me |

# killeraliens.github.io/doctors-near-me

Doctors Near Me is an app that locates and displays medical professionals based on your location, insurance plan, or specialty search inputs. This project utilizes OOJS & constructor functions to pull doctor info from highly nested JSON objects, as well as ES 2017 features to sequence multiple API calls for its filter results.

© Built with HTML5, CSS, jQuery, JavaScript, Better Doctor API, Google Maps JavaScript API, Google Geocoding and Reverse Geocoding APIs

## Goat's Guide | www.goatsguide.com

Goat's Guide is a heavy metal event & venue database concept as well as an ongoing study in UX design. I am currently reworking this project using React, Express/Node to reduce app loading time, and encourage user participation with the integration of Facebook's Graph API.

Current version is built with Ruby on Rails, and utilizes HTML-scraping gems such as Watir and Nokogiri, along with custom background tasks/Sidekiq to collect event data. Uses Devise gem for authentication. PostgreSQL database. Deployed with Heroku.

You can find more projects on my website at killeraliens.github.io/alexandra-brinn

### **EXPERIENCE**

APR 2015 - JUL 2018

# Burgeon Group | Design Project Manager | instagram @BurgeonGroup

Burgeon group is a niche design & build firm with a stellar international reputation for the concept, design, and fabrication of children's experience in the public library space. My role as design project manager included coordination between client , design, and fabrication departments. I worked closely with the CEO/lead designer contributing to client communications, design, and marketing, as well as executed the technical drafting, construction & installation plan documents for our inhouse fabrication teams

2012 - 2015

## Demi Coffee | instagram @DemiCoffee

Developed and operated a small food & beverage concept with a partner. Great experience in customer service, creative offerings, fun with branding. Best cold brew.

2012 - CURRENT

## Curiotile

Personal project in product design. Iterative flatpack designs in stainless and powedercoat steel, custom displays & storage solutions. Website coming soon.

2009 - 2013

# Ah Diós | Freelance Graphics & Branding

Collaborating with three others in web, film, and UX backgrounds. Brand development and various projects in graphic, signage, web, and packaging for Visual+Intent, Cartel Coffee Lab, Request Manufacturing, Sooh Media +